IULIAN DANIEL BOIAN

IRATA L3 Rope Access Technician

PERSONAL PROFILE

A focused professional with strong experience, skills, and knowledge that I gained for over 10 years as a Rope Access Technician. I am competent in all aspects of working at heights, narrow, and confined spaces. Additionally, I possess skills such as time management, organization, decision-making, problem resolution, and communication. I believe I possess the required capabilities to make a significant and beneficial contribution to your company.

EDUCATION

2007-2010

Bilingv Decebal High School, Bucharest, Romania Arts and Works skool group Spiru Haret UCECOM

1997-2000

CAR TINMAN AND PAINTER Vocational school Diploma

QUALIFICATIONS

FULL GWO, BLADE REPAIRS,
BASIC TECHNICAL TRAINING (BTT)
BOSIET, CA-EBS, OPITO, HUET
IRATA Level 3 Rope Access Technician
First Aid Certificate Level 3
CONFINED SPACE ENTRY & RESCUE

Right to work in UK and EU (VCR) Full UK driving license

OTHER MENTIONS

Sports (biking, rock climbing), Traveling Music enthusiast

FOREIGN LANGUAGES

English: Professional working proficiency

Romanian: Native

Telephone: +44 7727293439 Email: spideralpine@gmail.com Address: 66 Lothian Avenue, Hayes, UB4 0EH, London, UK

WORK EXPERIENCE

January - February 2024 3C METAL

Rope access and confined space rescue team leader Off-shore (Valaris DS-7)

November 2023 – present Muehlhan

Team leader, Maintenance Siemens wind turbines grinding sanding mastic tape, and painting

September - October 2023 Muehlhan

Team leader, maintenance of Vestas wind turbines, NDT paint test, replacement of nacelle screws, replacement of blade ring.

March - September 2023

CAN LTD Team leader in charge of rescue, and replacement of the O2 arena roof

August 2022 - February 2023 ARP ENERGY SERVICES LTD

Team leader in charge of rigging and rescue.

June-July 2022

Bilfinger - Level 3 Rope Access Team Leader

In charge of rescue, insulation, and maintenance at Shell onshore refinery.

June - November 2021

Muehlhan

Wind turbine maintenance Vestas Offshore work, Blasting, grinding, sanding, replacement of access stairs

February - June 2021

Rope Access Technician Elite Abseiling LTD - London

September 2020 - February 2021

Painting and decorating, fixing, glazing, mastic services

May - August 2020

Rope Access Technician ARP LTD - London Glazing and fixing services

March - April 2020

Rope Access Technician V Fixing LTD - London

UK* Mastic work and fixing Business or Construction sector

OTHER WORKING EXPERIENCE:

January - February 2020

Rope Access Technician CAN LTD - London UK* PTS* Vegetation cleaning* Night shift Business or Construction sector

November 2019 - January 2020

Rope Access Technician R.A.T. Services LTD - London UK* Panel lifting and fixing Business or Construction sector

November - November 2019

Rope Access Technician R.A.T. Services LTD - London UK* Window cleaning Business or Construction sector

October - October 2019

Rope Access Technician Rope Techs LTD - London UK* Mastic work Business or Construction sector

September - October 2019

Rope Access Technician R.A.T. Services LTD - London UK * Window cleaning Business or Construction sector

June - June 2019

Rope Access Technician FK LTD - London UK * Window cleaning Business or Construction sector

June - June 2019

Rope Access Technician CAN LTD - London

March - June 2019

UK * Install cable trace Business or Construction sector

March 2019

Rope Access Technician V Fixing LTD - London UK * Mastic work and fixing Business or Construction sector

February 2019

Rope Access Technician ARA Alternative Rope Access LTD - London

UK * Mastic work and fixing Business or Construction sector

February 2019

Rope Access Technician D&A LTD - London

October - November 2018

UK * Window fittings removed and changed Business or sector construction

February 2019

Rope Access Technician CAN LTD - London

July - September 2018

UK * Window and panel installation Business or sector Construction

August - December 2017

Rope Access Technician Total Solutions Direct LTD - London

July - August 2017

Rope Access Technician ARA Alternative Rope Access LTD - London

UK * Atrium window cleaning * Working at heights Business or sector Construction

June 2015 - June 2016

Tree Surgeon Petre e Legne - Corse

France * Trimming trees that affect the public networks * Trimming trees using mechanical tools (mechanical saws) * Cleaning debris before and after trimming * Correction trimming trees * Removing stumps and transporting timber results Business or sector Agriculture/Forestry

April 2012 - May 2015

Rope Access Technician SC Serv Telefib SRL - Bucharest, RO

And MW antennas (IDU and ODU upgrade) * Installing access points for customers * Site visits, estimating connectivity solutions * Installing optical fiber in the subway system * Electrical work * Installing solar panels * Civil work Business or sector IT/Telecom

January 2002 - June 2015 Rope Access Technician European Union

Window changing and fireproof system, working at heights in cradle Business or Construction sector.

June 2008 - February 2012

Rope Access Technician RCA Advanced Communication Networks - Bucharest, RO

Bucharest, Romania Installing/removal MW antennas: Ericsson, Nec, Alcatel, SIAE (0.3-3.2 m diameter). Antenna alignment Installing/removal RF antennas, RRUs, RBS (Ericsson, Huawei) Installing access points, OFDM's (AU/SU). Sites/Customers Site visits Civil work Business or sector IT/Telecom

March 2006 - March 2008 Workers/Technician SC Grand Alpin SRL - Bucharest, RO

Bucharest, Romania * Construction and assembly - Metal structures, wash/repair curtain walls, bond and trespa assembly, cladding polystyrene, exterior coatings * Advertising - Mounting structure banner * Ambient lighting and landscaping * Measurements and special interventions - Cutting trees, paint and sandblast metal structures Business or sector Workers/Technician